export const Questions = [
  {
    prompt: 'Which of this is not a programming language?',
    optionA: 'Python',
    optionB: 'JavaScript',
    optionC: 'MC-03',
    optionD: 'Java',
    answer: 'C'
  },

  {
    prompt: 'What does the term "DOM" stand for in JavaScript?',
    optionA: 'Document Object Model',
    optionB: 'Data Object Model',
    optionC: 'Dynamic Operation Model',
    optionD: 'Document Oriented Middleware',
    answer: 'A'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'What keyword is used to declare variables in JavaScript?',
    optionA: 'var',
    optionB: 'int',
    optionC: 'declare',
    optionD: 'variable',
    answer: 'A'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'Which of the following is a falsy value in JavaScript?',
    optionA: '0 (number)',
    optionB: '" " (empty string)',
    optionC: 'false (boolean)',
    optionD: 'All of the above',
    answer: 'D'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'What is the purpose of the typeof operator in JavaScript?',
    optionA: 'To check if a variable is defined',
    optionB: 'To determine the type of a variable',
    optionC: 'To convert a variable to a different type',
    optionD: 'To declare a variable',
    answer: 'B'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'What does the === operator do in JavaScript?',
    optionA: 'Assigns a value to a variable',
    optionB: 'Compares the values and types of two variables',
    optionC: 'Concatenates two strings3',
    optionD: 'Checks if a variable is null',
    answer: 'B'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'Which of this is not a javascript framework?',
    optionA: 'React',
    optionB: 'Angular',
    optionC: 'Vue',
    optionD: 'Java',
    answer: 'D'
  },
  {
    prompt:
      'Which function is used to print something in the console in JavaScript?',
    optionA: 'console.print()',
    optionB: 'print()',
    optionC: 'log()',
    optionD: 'write()',
    answer: 'C'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'What is an anonymous function in JavaScript?',
    optionA: 'A function without a name',
    optionB: 'A function with an undefined return value',
    optionC: 'A function that is automatically callede',
    optionD: 'A function that only takes anonymous arguments',
    answer: 'A'
  },
  {
    prompt: 'How do you comment a single line in JavaScript?',
    optionA: '/* Comment */',
    optionB: '// Comment',
    optionC: '-- Comment',
    optionD: "' Comment ",
    answer: 'B'
  }
];
